Eduarda Ferreira Lima

Alameda, California, Brazilian, 24 years old ferreiraduda99@gmail.com +1 (341) 758 3440

<u>Objective:</u> Professional with 5 years of experience in finance and tech industries, primarily in program management positions, aiming at joining Business Analyst in order to continue developing skills in good documentation, reporting, analyses and communication.

Education

Computer Science, Universidade Nove de Julho, São Paulo, SP - 2017 to 2021

Professional Experience

AMAZON WEB SERVICE BRAZIL - Program Manager Junior - 2021 to 2022

- Worked cross-functionally with AWS LATAM teams, including solution architects, customer solution managers, partners, and marketing, to analyze and map KPIs and lead the implementation of Asana Software on AWS Brazil as part of the Solution Architects' project management
- Ensured that all initiatives were executed following the company's compliance
- Responsible for supporting managers, directors, and executives in monitoring the strategic goals of each IC
- Led LATAM initiatives from end to end, conducting requirements such as writing press releases, building surveys, brainstorming the development of new solutions, and assuring the deliveries at each stage
- Prepared management reports, tracked and monitored KPIs, and provided assistance to support strategic areas such as automating the control of HC per Customer for our directors
- Updated internal websites and reported on the control of the LATAM quarterly results
- Organized small, medium, and large-scale events (online and in person), managing budgets and reducing more than \$30,000.00 through negotiations with sponsors between 2020 and 2022
- Provided an updated analysis and documented the progress of strategic indicators using Tableau and Salesforce CRM
- Internship Amazon Web Service 2019/2020, hired as a full time employee in 2021

SANTANDER BANK BRAZIL - Commercial Assistant Legal Entity in Agency - 2017 to 2019

- Responsible for implementing the company's business practices, ensuring greater harmony and maintenance among the account managers
- Responsible for establishing and overseeing product metrics using data reports to support stakeholders' decision-making process
- Responsible for managing the legal entity portfolio in the São Paulo region, offering customer service and support whenever necessary
- Responsible for delivering comprehensive customer service when needed, converting 20% of individual accounts into legal entity accounts
- Internship at Santander Bank Commercial Area in 2017/2018

Additional Information

- Participated in two Young Apprentices programs, one with General Motors and the other with Santander Bank
- Led the AWS Latam Studio initiative as a co-producer and co-owner, designed to scale with the latest in video and podcast modes, delivering over 75% of the content across top streamers and reaching over 10K listeners
- Was recognized among the Santander and Universia branch network for the "Projeto Os Mestres"

Languages: Portuguese (Native), English (Advanced), Spanish (Intermediate)

Computing: AWS CLOUD Architecture; Salesforce Customer 360; Tableau; Asana; Microsoft Office Package; Adobe Premiere; Illustrator; Lightroom; SQL; HTML; CSS; JavaScript; Python; Java

International Experience: Expanish School Buenos Aires, Argentina (2018); AWS Workshop, Seattle, USA (2021); Au Pair Program, San Francisco, USA (2023)

Keywords: Computer science, IT, project management, communication, customer service, program management, requirements survey, solution development, process analysis, management reports, KPI, analysis and data, Tableau, Salesforce CRM, automation